{
	"response_code": 0,
	"results": [
		{
			"category": "Vehicles",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "The%20Italian%20automaker%20Lamborghini%20uses%20what%20animal%20as%20its%20logo%3F",
			"correct_answer": "Bull",
			"incorrect_answers": ["Bat", "Horse", "Snake"]
		},
		{
			"category": "Vehicles",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20car%20manufacturers%20had%20a%20war%20named%20after%20it%3F",
			"correct_answer": "Toyota",
			"incorrect_answers": ["Honda", "Ford", "Volkswagen"]
		},
		{
			"category": "Vehicles",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20collision%20avoidance%20systems%20helps%20airplanes%20avoid%20colliding%20with%20each%20other%3F",
			"correct_answer": "TCAS",
			"incorrect_answers": ["GPWS", "OCAS", "TAWS"]
		},
		{
			"category": "Vehicles",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "Which%20of%20these%20companies%20does%20NOT%20manufacture%20motorcycles%3F",
			"correct_answer": "Toyota",
			"incorrect_answers": ["Honda", "Kawasaki", "Yamaha"]
		},
		{
			"category": "Vehicles",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "Which%20car%20tire%20manufacturer%20is%20famous%20for%20its%20%22Eagle%22%20brand%20of%20tires%2C%20and%20is%20the%20official%20tire%20supplier%20of%20NASCAR%3F",
			"correct_answer": "Goodyear",
			"incorrect_answers": ["Pirelli", "Bridgestone", "Michelin"]
		},
		{
			"category": "Vehicles",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "Which%20car%20tire%20manufacturer%20is%20famous%20for%20its%20%22P%20Zero%22%20line%3F",
			"correct_answer": "Pirelli",
			"incorrect_answers": ["Goodyear", "Bridgestone", "Michelin"]
		},
		{
			"category": "Vehicles",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "The%20LS1%20engine%20is%20how%20many%20cubic%20inches%3F",
			"correct_answer": "346",
			"incorrect_answers": ["350", "355", "360"]
		},
		{
			"category": "Vehicles",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "The%20LS7%20engine%20is%20how%20many%20cubic%20inches%3F",
			"correct_answer": "427",
			"incorrect_answers": ["346", "364", "376"]
		},
		{
			"category": "Vehicles",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "The%20LS3%20engine%20is%20how%20many%20cubic%20inches%3F",
			"correct_answer": "376",
			"incorrect_answers": ["346", "364", "427"]
		},
		{
			"category": "Vehicles",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20Nissan%27s%20most%20popular%20electric%20car%3F",
			"correct_answer": "Leaf",
			"incorrect_answers": ["Tree", "Deer", "Roots"]
		}
	]
}
